http://www.hocm.org/privacy-policy/

Hands On Children's Museum
Plan Your VisitHours and AdmissionsCOVID-19Blackbaud Security IncidentPersonal Play DateFirst-Time VisitorsDirections & ParkingMuseum FAQNewsletterSpecial Guests & ActivitiesToursExhibit GalleriesPlay Day CafeMuseum StoreGift CertificatesArea AttractionsSensory Friendly GuideEast Bay Public Plaza Temporarily ClosedCalendar414 Jefferson St. NE
Olympia, WA 98501
Get Directions(360) 956-0818Events & ProgramsEventsBoo Bash!Summer Splash! Daytime FestivalSummer Splash! Evening GalaDental Health Month 2020Virtual Art GalleryVirtual Pet ParadeProgramsFirst Friday NightMakeSpaceNature PlaySensory-Friendly EventsCalendarLearn With UsKids/TeachersCampsFall CampsWinter CampsPreschoolField Trips & Group VisitsMusic TogetherDr. ScienceHands On 2U@HomeParentsCandyce BollingerPlayWisePowerParentingPartner ProgramsCalendarBirthdays/Private EventsBirthdaysHave Your Birthday HereGift CertificatesPrivate EventsWeddingsHost a MeetingJoinBecome A Member Today!Corporate MembersGet InvolvedBecome an EmployeeDonate
E-Newsletter
Facebook
Twitter
GiveDonateBuy a Frog or FishLeadership CircleDonate
E-Newsletter
Facebook
Twitter
Gift CertificatesOpen Today Closed
Privacy Policy
Home  >  About Us  >  Privacy Policy
Personal Information
The Hands On Children’s Museum only collects personal information when you request our services and only uses the information collected to provide those services for you.  If you choose to make a donation or purchase, you will be asked to provide contact information (such as your name and shipping address) and financial information (such as your credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to process your order. The Hands On Children’s Museum handles all of this data with the utmost confidentiality.
Third Parties
Any personal information provided will not be traded, rented, sold or otherwise shared with anyone outside of the Hands On Children’s Museum, or used for reasons beyond those contemplated in this statement. From time to time, we may engage third parties to process your information on our behalf; however, none of the Hands On Children’s Museum affiliates (such as our credit card company) have permission to retain, share, store or use personal information for any reason other than providing the requested service.
Security
To prevent unauthorized access, disclosure and improper use of your information, we have established appropriate safeguards to protect the information we collect in accordance with our privacy policy.
Photo/Video Policy within the MuseumEach person entering the Hands On Children’s Museum grants the museum permission to photograph, videotape, record or otherwise reproduce the image and/or voice of that person and all accompanying minors, without compensation, for the museum’s business purposes, including copying, distribution, and other uses.
IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE PHOTOGRAPHED, please inform the front desk upon check-in and request a NO PHOTO sticker to place on your child. Our staff, volunteers, and visiting media are instructed to look for the stickers and will do their best to avoid including your child in materials. Large crowd shots where individuals are not identifiable may still occur.
Privacy Policy
About UsOur New HomeNewsBoard MembersPartner OrganizationsInspired Learning for All Initiative - WSECUFree & Reduced ProgramsContact UsAwardsEmployment
